http://ronlynn.com/privacy-policy.php

Privacy Policy
RLM Apparel Software Privacy Policy
RLM Apparel Software, Inc.
160 Chubb Avenue
Suite 205
Lyndhurst, NJ 07071
marydean@ronlynn.com
201.531.5959 (main)
201.531.0999 (fax)
www.ronlynn.com
RLM Apparel Software collects personal data sent through their Enterprise Software System by RLM’s Clients to fulfill, said clients, Customers orders.  We collect our Client’s Customers, Name, Email, Shipping and Billing Address, Payment details, Shipment details.
We need this information to provide Services, including supporting and processing orders, shipping, authentication, and processing payments.
Description of Activities:
RLM Apparel Software, Inc. uses this data to ship orders to the end customers of the RLM Apparel Software’s client.
RLM Apparel Software, Inc. only uses personal information for the purposes of transacting a shipment to the Client’s end Customer. This would include sending Customers order information at Client’s request to a 3rd party software that could be in use by a Client, so that third parties may process and ship the Customers order to the appropriate address location along with the products purchased by the Customer.
Collection of Personal Information:
RLM Apparel Software, Inc Client enters their end Customers information directly into RLM software or the end Customers data is transmitted into RLM Apparel Software, Inc. by a third-party software contracted by said Client.  RLM Apparel Software, Inc. is acting as a conduit for data transmitted by third parties.
Who Do We Share the Information With:
Under no circumstances does RLM share client’s customer information with 3rd parties unless required by RLM's client for the purposes of fulfilling the needs of their internal business operations. This includes, but is not limited to warehouse management companies, Factors, Payment Processors, Wholesale Order Management companies, e-commerce providers, financial institutions, and Point of Sales Systems on behalf of RLM’s Clients directive.
Description of Organization Privacy Policy for Such Personal Information:
RLM Apparel Software’s official website is www.ronlynn.com and the Privacy Shield link is located at the bottom of the home page
The effective date of implementation is March 16, 2018
Contact office for handling complaints. Access requests, and any other issues arising under the Privacy Shield:
RLM Apparel Software, Inc.
160 Chubb Avenue
Suite 205
Lyndhurst, NJ 07071
201.531.5959 (main)
201.531.0999 (fax)
www.ronlynn.com
RLM Apparel Software, Inc. is a member of the Privacy Shield and the EU DPA
Affirmative commitment to comply with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework:
RLM Apparel Software, Inc. complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States.  RLM Apparel Software, Inc. has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles.  If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/
Independent Recourse Mechanism for Privacy Shield Complaints:
In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, RLM Apparel Software, Inc. commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information.  EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact RLM Apparel Software, Inc. at:
RLM Apparel Software, Inc.
Attn: Mary Dean
160 Chubb Avenue
Suite 205
Lyndhurst, NJ 07071
marydean@ronlynn.com
201.531.5959 (main)
201.531.0999 (fax)
www.ronlynn.com
The Self-assessment must be signed by a corporate officer once per year and made available upon request by individuals or in the context of an investigation or a complaint about non-compliance.
RLM Apparel Software, Inc. has further committed to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) regarding unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning data transferred from the EU.
RLM Apparel Software, Inc. only provides Customers information to a third party upon the request of RLM Apparel Software, Inc. Client in order to fulfill Client’s Customer orders or to process a Client’s Customer payment.
RLM Apparel Software, Inc. gives the right of individuals to access their personal data upon request.
RLM Apparel Software, Inc. does not provide Customer’s Client information to third parties outside of the scope of normal business functions.
RLM Apparel Software, Inc. may be subject to investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC).
RLM Apparel Software, Inc. understands and accepts the possibility, under certain conditions, for the individual to invoke binding arbitration.
RLM Apparel Software, Inc. accepts and adheres to the requirements to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
RLM Apparel Software, Inc. is responsible for all onward transfers of Personal Information to third parties in accordance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework.
RLM Apparel Software, Inc. will always ask for consent before sharing Personal Information with third parties for purposes other than those described above.
RLM Apparel Software will continue to store archived copies of Client’s Customer’s data for legitimate business purposes and to comply with the law.
RLM Apparel Software, Inc. will never share, disclose, sell, rent, or otherwise provide Personal Information to other companies for marketing of their own products or services.
We do not use the Personal Information we collect from Clients or Client’s Customers to independently contact or market to Client’s Customers.
Securing Personal Information:
We follow industry standards on information security management to safeguard sensitive information, such as financial information, intellectual property, employee details and any other Personal Information entrusted to us. Our information security systems apply to people, processes and information technology systems on a risk management basis.
Control and Access to Personal Information:
You retain all rights to your Personal Information and can access it anytime. In addition, RLM Apparel Software, Inc. takes reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Information. You can update many types of Personal Information, such as payment or contact information. It’s important to remember that if you delete or limit the use of your Personal Information, the Services may not function properly.
If you have any questions about your Personal Information or this policy, or if you would like to make a complaint about how RLM Apparel Software, Inc. processes your personal data, please contact RLM Apparel Software, Inc. at 201.531.5959.
